Brody, David Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers 6241
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
David Brody Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers
1993-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brody, David
6241
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
6188931
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6220: U.S. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations (Dunlop Commission) Documents 6262: Thomas A. Kochan Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers
Appelbaum, Eileen, 1940-; Beaumont, Richard A.; Brody, David; Freeman, Richard; Knicely, Howard V.; Rogers, Joel, 1952-; Sola, Stephen Andrew; Yager, Daniel V.; George Meany Center for Labor Studies; ILR Labor Law Reform Conference; United States. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations
6188931
- ILR. Labor Law Reform Conference. Correspondence., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ILR. Labor Law Reform Conference. Papers., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies. Seminar for Secretary-Treasurers. Proceedings., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dunlop Commission. Appelbaum, Eileen. Testimony., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dunlop Commission. Beaumont, Richard A. Statement., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dunlop Commission. Brody, David. Statement., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dunlop Commission. Knicely, Howard V. Statement., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dunlop Commission. Rogers, Joel. Statement., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dunlop Commission. Rogers, Joel and Richard Freeman. Statement., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dunlop Commission. Sola, Stephen Andrew. Statement., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dunlop Commission. Yager, Daniel V. Statement., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dunlop Commission. Papers., 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- TEAM Act. Papers., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)